<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on YUKI-Blog</title>
    <link>https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on YUKI-Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yuki and Koko</title>
      <link>https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/yuki_and_fox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/yuki_and_fox/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, there was a 7-year-old girl named Yuki who loved to explore the forest. One day, she stumbled upon a small fox that was lost and scared. Yuki took the fox in and named it Koko. They became fast friends and had many adventures in the woods.
As time went on, Yuki realized that Koko needed to find his family. So, she set out to help him.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://itsyukispace.tech/images/2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;this is picture&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time, there was a 7-year-old girl named Yuki who loved to explore the forest. One day, she stumbled upon a small fox that was lost and scared. Yuki took the fox in and named it Koko. They became fast friends and had many adventures in the woods.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As time went on, Yuki realized that Koko needed to find his family. So, she set out to help him. Together, they searched the forest and eventually found Koko&amp;rsquo;s parents and siblings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although Yuki was sad to say goodbye, she was happy to see Koko reunited with his family. She promised to visit often and continue to explore the forest with a newfound appreciation for the animals that lived there.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuki and her friends` story</title>
      <link>https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/yuki_and_her_friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/yuki_and_her_friends/</guid>
      <description>Yuki is a 7-year-old girl who loves spending time with her friends Kennedy, Abby, Wyter and Annika. One sunny day, they were playing in the park when Yuki suggested they play hide and seek. Everyone is excited, so they quickly get started.
Yuki covers her eyes and starts counting while the other kids run and hide. yuki looks around and tries to figure out where they might go. She looked behind the trees and bushes, under the slides and swings, but no one was there.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Yuki is a 7-year-old girl who loves spending time with her friends Kennedy, Abby, Wyter and Annika. One sunny day, they were playing in the park when Yuki suggested they play hide and seek. Everyone is excited, so they quickly get started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yuki covers her eyes and starts counting while the other kids run and hide. yuki looks around and tries to figure out where they might go. She looked behind the trees and bushes, under the slides and swings, but no one was there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yuki got a little frustrated, but she didn&amp;rsquo;t want to give up. She closed her eyes again, counted to ten, and then resumed her search. This time, she thought she heard giggling from behind the big oak tree. yuki ran to the tree, but there was no one there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, Yuki felt someone tap her on the shoulder. She turned around and saw Kennedy, behind whom she had been hiding. Kennedy giggles and tries to keep quiet, but Yuki spots her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, Yuki and Kennedy look for the others. They look everywhere, but they can&amp;rsquo;t find anyone. yuki is about to give up when she sees a sneaker peeking out from behind a bush. It was Abby! She had found a perfect hiding place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One by one, Yuki found Wyter and Annika. they were both laughing and having fun, but they knew the game wasn&amp;rsquo;t over yet. They decided to play it again in a different way, with Yuki hiding first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was a wonderful day, full of laughter and adventure. yuki and her friends felt they could conquer the world and nothing could stop them. They knew they had each other&amp;rsquo;s backs, and no matter what, they would always be there for each other.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yuki`s first story</title>
      <link>https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://itsyukispace.tech/posts/hello/</guid>
      <description>Yuki was a curious and creative 7-year-old girl who loved to make things with her hands. One day, she decided to make a boat using clay, and she went to work.
Step 1: Yuki took a ball of clay and rolled it into a long, thin shape like a snake.
Step 2: Then, she bent the clay into a U-shape to make the hull of the boat, and used a small tool to create a seat for a tiny clay figurine to sit.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Yuki was a &lt;code&gt;curious&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;creative&lt;/code&gt; 7-year-old girl who loved to make things with her hands. One day, she &lt;code&gt;decided to&lt;/code&gt; make a boat using clay, and she went to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Step 1&lt;/code&gt;: Yuki took a ball of clay and rolled it into a long, thin shape like a snake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Step 2&lt;/code&gt;: Then, she bent the clay into a U-shape to make the &lt;code&gt;hull of the boat&lt;/code&gt;, and used a small tool to create a seat for a &lt;code&gt;tiny clay figurine&lt;/code&gt; to sit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Step 3&lt;/code&gt;: Finally, Yuki added a small piece of clay on top of the hull to make the &lt;code&gt;mast&lt;/code&gt; of the boat, and she &lt;code&gt;gently&lt;/code&gt; pressed a small &lt;code&gt;triangle&lt;/code&gt; shape of clay to create a &lt;code&gt;sail&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yuki was thrilled with her new boat, and she placed the tiny clay &lt;code&gt;figurine&lt;/code&gt; in the seat. She imagined the figurine &lt;code&gt;sailing&lt;/code&gt; the high seas and &lt;code&gt;discovering&lt;/code&gt; new lands. Yuki was proud
&lt;img src=&#34;https://itsyukispace.tech/images/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;this is picture&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
